{"VocabFREE" : [
  {
    "Question":"aeon",
    "Answer":"an indefinitely long period of time; an age."
  },
  {
    "Question":"affectation",
    "Answer":"behavior that is assumed rather than natural; artificiality."
  },
  {
    "Question":"aloof",
    "Answer":"distant physically or emotionally; reserved and remote"
  },
  {
    "Question":"amalgam",
    "Answer":"a combination of diverse elements; a mixture."
  },
  {
    "Question":"ambivalent",
    "Answer":"having opposing attitude or feelings about something."
  },
  {
    "Question":"anguish",
    "Answer":"agonizing physical or mental pain; torment."
  },
  {
    "Question":"antecedent",
    "Answer":"one that precedes another"
  },
  {
    "Question":"apathy",
    "Answer":"indifference"
  },
  {
    "Question":"aplomb",
    "Answer":"self-confident assurance; poise"
  },
  {
    "Question":"appall",
    "Answer":"to fill with consternation or dismay"
  },
  {
    "Question":"apropos",
    "Answer":"to the point."
  },
  {
    "Question":"archaic",
    "Answer":"of, relating to, or characteristic of words and language that were once common but are now used chiefly to suggest an earlier style or period."
  },
  {
    "Question":"arduous",
    "Answer":"testing severely the powers of endurance; strenuous."
  },
  {
    "Question":"assertive",
    "Answer":"incined to bold or confident assertion; aggressively self-assured."
  },
  {
    "Question":"auspicious",
    "Answer":"favorable."
  },
  {
    "Question":"automaton",
    "Answer":"something that behaves like a robot."
  },
  {
    "Question":"avant-garde",
    "Answer":"a group active in the invention and application of new techniques in a given field, especially in the arts."
  },
  {
    "Question":"avarice",
    "Answer":"greed."
  },
  {
    "Question":"banality",
    "Answer":"something that is trite, obvious, or predictable; a commonplace"
  },
  {
    "Question":"bane",
    "Answer":"fatal injury or ruin"
  },
  {
    "Question":"beleaguered",
    "Answer":"to harass; beset"
  },
  {
    "Question":"belie",
    "Answer":"to picture falsely; misrepresent."
  },
  {
    "Question":"belligerent",
    "Answer":"inclined or eager to fight; hostile or aggressive."
  },
  {
    "Question":"bipartisan",
    "Answer":"supported by two political parties"
  },
  {
    "Question":"blight",
    "Answer":"any of numerous plant diseases resulting in sudden conspicuous wilting and dying of affected parts, especially young, growing tissues."
  },
  {
    "Question":"bog",
    "Answer":"a wetland."
  },
  {
    "Question":"bolster",
    "Answer":"to support"
  },
  {
    "Question":"boon",
    "Answer":"a benefit bestowed"
  },
  {
    "Question":"bowdlerize",
    "Answer":"to remove offensive portions from a book."
  },
  {
    "Question":"burgeon",
    "Answer":"to grow and flourish"
  },
  {
    "Question":"celerity",
    "Answer":"swiftness of action or motion; speed."
  },
  {
    "Question":"chronological",
    "Answer":"arranged in order of time of occurrence."
  },
  {
    "Question":"circumscribe",
    "Answer":"to limit narrowly; restrict."
  },
  {
    "Question":"circumvent",
    "Answer":"to avoid or get around by artful meaneuvering"
  },
  {
    "Question":"clamor",
    "Answer":"a loud outcry; a hubbub"
  },
  {
    "Question":"colloquial",
    "Answer":"informal speech or writing"
  },
  {
    "Question":"complaisant",
    "Answer":"exhibiting a desire or willingness to please; cheerfully obliging"
  },
  {
    "Question":"condemn",
    "Answer":"to express strong disapproval of."
  },
  {
    "Question":"conjecture",
    "Answer":"a guess based on incomplete evidence."
  },
  {
    "Question":"cordial",
    "Answer":"friendly"
  },
  {
    "Question":"cosmopolitan",
    "Answer":"having constituent elements from many different parts of the world."
  },
  {
    "Question":"covet",
    "Answer":"to desire"
  },
  {
    "Question":"cynical",
    "Answer":"scornful of the motives, virtue or integrity of others"
  },
  {
    "Question":"daunting",
    "Answer":"discouraging"
  },
  {
    "Question":"dearth",
    "Answer":"a scarce supply; a lack"
  },
  {
    "Question":"deficient",
    "Answer":"lacking an essential quality or element."
  },
  {
    "Question":"deft",
    "Answer":"skillful."
  },
  {
    "Question":"deleterious",
    "Answer":"having a harmful effect; injurious"
  },
  {
    "Question":"demur",
    "Answer":"to voice opposition; object"
  },
  {
    "Question":"denounce",
    "Answer":"to condemn openly as being evil or reprehensible"
  },
  {
    "Question":"deter",
    "Answer":"to prevent or discourage from acting, as by means of fear or doubt."
  },
  {
    "Question":"devour",
    "Answer":"to eat or ingest."
  },
  {
    "Question":"diffident",
    "Answer":"lacking or marked by a lack of self-confidence; shy and timid"
  },
  {
    "Question":"diletante",
    "Answer":"a dabbler in an art or field of knowledge"
  },
  {
    "Question":"diminution",
    "Answer":"lessening or reduction."
  },
  {
    "Question":"diminutive",
    "Answer":"extremely small in size; tiny"
  },
  {
    "Question":"dirge",
    "Answer":"a funeral song."
  },
  {
    "Question":"dissolute",
    "Answer":"lacking moral restraint; indulging in sensual pleasures or vices."
  },
  {
    "Question":"divisive",
    "Answer":"creating dissension or discord."
  },
  {
    "Question":"dogmatic",
    "Answer":"characterized by an authoritative, arrogant assertion of unproved or unprovable principles."
  },
  {
    "Question":"don",
    "Answer":"to put on (clothing)"
  },
  {
    "Question":"dour",
    "Answer":"unyielding; stubborn."
  },
  {
    "Question":"droll",
    "Answer":"amusingly odd or whimsically comical."
  },
  {
    "Question":"dynamic",
    "Answer":"marked by energy."
  },
  {
    "Question":"economical",
    "Answer":"affordable"
  },
  {
    "Question":"effusive",
    "Answer":"profuse; overflowing; unrestrained or excessive in emotional expression; gushy."
  },
  {
    "Question":"elaborate",
    "Answer":"to express at greater length or in greater detail."
  },
  {
    "Question":"elan",
    "Answer":"enthusiastic vigor or liveliness"
  },
  {
    "Question":"elistist",
    "Answer":"the belieft that certain persons or members of certain classes/groups deserve favored treatment by virtue of their perceived superiortiy, as in intellect, social status or finances"
  },
  {
    "Question":"elusive",
    "Answer":"hard to track"
  },
  {
    "Question":"emote",
    "Answer":"to express emotion, especially in an excessive or theatrical manner."
  },
  {
    "Question":"empathy",
    "Answer":"identification with and understand of another's situation, feelings and motives."
  },
  {
    "Question":"empirical",
    "Answer":"relying on or derived from observation or experiment."
  },
  {
    "Question":"enrapture",
    "Answer":"to fill with delight."
  },
  {
    "Question":"enumerate",
    "Answer":"to count off or name one by one; list."
  },
  {
    "Question":"envelop",
    "Answer":"to enclose or encase completely with or as if with a covering."
  },
  {
    "Question":"ephemeral",
    "Answer":"lasting for a markedly brief time."
  },
  {
    "Question":"epitomie",
    "Answer":"to be a typical example of."
  },
  {
    "Question":"euphoric",
    "Answer":"a feeling of great happiness."
  }
]
}